(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-28T12:26:52.196249",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo
最高な時間 最高の仲間と
With the best time, with the best friends,
キラメキに乗って☆ （イエーイ！）
Riding on the sparkle☆ (Yay!)
覚えてるかな？最初の歌 （懐かしいね）
Can you remember our very first song? (Such fond memories)
私 声が震えてた （ほんの少し）
My voice was trembling (Just a little bit)
あの日から続く未来は みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
The future continuing from that day is today, seized together with everyone.
もっともっともっともっともっと 加速するハート （一緒に）
My heart accelerates more and more and more (Together)
行くよ どこまでも
Let's go, no matter where.
(Are you ready?) 準備はOK！
(Are you ready?) We're all set, OK!
ひらけ！！夢のトビラを (1, 2, 3) （キラメキライダー☆）
Open the doors to our dreams!! (1, 2, 3) (Kirameki Rider☆)
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう 最高な時間 最高の仲間と
Let's make our newborn heartbeats echo with the best time and best friends,
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me.
君に会いたくて やってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I wanted to see you, that's why I came here. Let's sing together!
終わらないメロディ キラメキに乗って☆
A never-ending melody, riding on the sparkle☆
キラメキに乗って☆
Riding on the sparkle☆
だから
That's why
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き 大好き！溢れるこの想い
I love you so, so, so, so much! This overflowing feeling
きっともっと止まらない♡
Will surely never stop ♡
あいあい あいあい ♡ あいらぶゆー 君が あいあい あいあい ♡ あい にじゅー
Ai-ai, ai-ai ♡ I love you, you are ai-ai, ai-ai ♡ I need you
もっと もっと もっと もっと！
More, and more, and more, and more!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
ぎゅっ愛させて
Hold me tight and let me love you
ユメミルハンドがぴょんぴょんぴょん
My dreaming hands go pyon pyon pyon
あー何落っことしあみゃみゃ
Ah, what did I drop, amyamya
こんなになってもいまだ抜け出せない
Even after becoming like this, I still can't escape
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい
What should I do, nuinui
たすけて君好きアホイホイ
Help me, I love you, ahoihoi
もっともっともっともっともっと
More, more, more, more, more
好きだけ愛してね！
Just love me as much as I like you!
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった
I got into anime and wanted to sing!
推しのシーン見ながら カラオケ歌えるなんて…
Being able to karaoke while watching my favorite scenes...
尊すぎてつらいっ！
Is too precious, it hurts!
歌いたい曲見つけよう！
Let's find the song you want to sing!
大賛成だ！
Totally agree!
全国のアミューズメント施設にて ホロライブ3期生 プライズ順次展開中！
Hololive 3rd Gen prizes rolling out sequentially at amusement facilities nationwide!
全国のアミューズメント施設でGETしてね♪
Get them at amusement facilities nationwide♪
吉野家で、ごはんしよっ！
Let's have a meal at Yoshinoya!
元祖の本気、召し上がれ。
Taste the original's seriousness.
牛丼は吉野家
Gyudon is Yoshinoya.
今日も、吉野家日和です。
Today is also a great Yoshinoya day.
本ラインナップ4種を含む新商品も今後登場予定！
More new products including these 4 items coming soon!
詳細は後日発表、お楽しみに♪
Details announced later, stay tuned♪
「ぬくもり竜宮ガール」GMVにご出演の豪華な声優陣が歌う
Featuring popular voice actors from the "Nukumori Ryuguu Girl" GMV singing
つながるぐるぐるマスコット！全国のガシャポン自販機で発売予定
Connected Guruguru Mascots! Coming to Gashapon machines nationwide
キラキラ金未来大作戦！
Sparkling Golden Future Operation!
せーの！
Ready, set!
はりきって行こう！ホロライブ3rdジェネレーションライブ
Let's get excited for Hololive 3rd Generation Live,
きゅるるん大作戦！
Kyururun Operation!
最強アイドルおすしかないでしょうにご来場いただき
Thank you for coming to see the strongest idols you can't help but support!
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内をさせていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live performance until the very end, we would like to make a few announcements.
公演中の撮影、録音、録画の仕様は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and video recording during the performance are strictly prohibited.
館内は禁煙となっております。
Smoking is prohibited inside the building.
喫煙はご遠慮ください。
Please refrain from smoking.
万が一具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
In the unlikely event that you feel unwell, please do not push yourself and notify nearby staff.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブやステージに物を投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
Mosh pits, stage diving, throwing objects onto the stage, and any behavior that causes trouble for others or disrupts the performance are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね。
Please follow the rules and have a great time.
はーい！
Okay!
また、本公演は映像配信及び写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合があります。
Also, cameras for live streaming and photography will be inside the venue, and seats may be captured on camera.
これら映像や写真はプロモーション等に使用される可能性がありますので、
These videos and photos may be used for promotions and other purposes,
あらかじめご了承下さい。
so please understand in advance.
また、ライブのハッシュタグは #きゅるるん大作戦DAY1 です。
Also, the live hashtag is #KyururunDaisakusenDAY1.
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてくれると嬉しいです！
We would be so happy if you use the hashtag to hype it up!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！
Well then, it's almost time for the show to start!
みんなの声をたくさん聞かせてね！
Let us hear your voices loud and clear!
それでは3期生、エンジン行くぞー！
Now then, 3rd Gen, let's rev our engines!
おー！
Yeah!
皆さん、今からマイクがなくなるので、静かに…静かに…。
Everyone, microphones will be turned off starting now, so please be quiet... quiet...
アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・ラブ・ユー もうアイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・にじゅう
I-I-I-I-I love you! Already i-i-i-i-i twenty—
もっと！もっと！もっと！もっと！ 好きなだけ愛させて！
More! More! More! More! Let me love you as much as I want!
サインしてライブ イッてこー！
Sign it and let's go live!
みんなで最高の思い出作ろね！ ふーん！
Let's make the best memories together! Fuun!
トルテルのない君だらけ
Overflowing with you, who has no faults,
ドカしてる胸は私
my heart is pounding,
心動悸動悸なってる警報は！
that alarming thumping in my chest!
毎日幻覚現れて 頭に話しちゃって
Hallucinations appear every day, talking in my head—
こういうやつは非常識ですわ！
someone like this is outrageous!
いっそ食べちゃいたい フリーズした感情
I'd rather just eat you up! Frozen emotions—
誰もが持ってるおねがい！
everyone has this wish!
ジュンジュジューモンエシャ とどめてきゅうじょうしょう
Conjuring a spell to halt and save you,
これが恋ならもう後悔しないわ！
if this is love, I have no regrets!
だから君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き
That's why I love you so, so, so, so, so much!
あふれるこの愛はきっともっと止まらない
This overflowing love surely won't stop growing.
アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・ラブ・ユー 君がアイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・アイ・にじゅう
I-I-I-I-I love you! You are i-i-i-i-i twenty—
もっと！もっと！もっと！もっと！ 気になったって愛させて
More! More! More! More! Let me love you even if you're curious!
揺るるハートがぴょんぴょんぴょん 穴に落ちてあわわわ
A swaying heart goes pyon-pyon-pyon, falling down a hole, oh no!
こんなになっても今だ抜け出せない
Even like this, I still can't escape!
どうしたもんかのぬいぬいぬい 助けて君たびあほいほい
What should I do, nui-nui-nui? Help me, you're all ahoy-hoy!
もっと！もっと！もっと！もっと！ 気になったって愛してね！
More! More! More! More! Love me even if you're curious!
ワクワクカブル夢のおなか
Inside a thrilling, bubbly dream,
君の声で目が覚めた ５感全部が君なしじゃ狂う
I woke up to your voice—without you, all five senses go crazy!
毎度お騒がせごめん きゅんで壊れちゃいそうだ
Sorry for always making a fuss, I feel like I'll break from cuteness!
こういってやつは制御不能ですわ！
Someone like this is uncontrollable!
いっそ抱きしめて 壊してもいいよ
Just hold me tight, you can even break me!
誰にも邪魔はさせない！
I won't let anyone get in the way!
ピチピチ感情で キラキラキュウ展開
Sparkling, rapid development with bubbling emotions!
これが運命ならもう迷わない！
If this is destiny, I'll never get lost again!
だから君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好きだいっじゅき
That's why I love you so, so, so, so, so much!
私のこの愛はきっとずっとも離さない
My love will surely never let you go!
ビビビマイベイビー あの日スキスキスキスキスキスキ
Bibibi my baby, ever since that day, like, like, like, like, like, like!
もっと！もっと！もっと！もっと！ 私だけを見ててね！
More! More! More! More! Only look at me!
いじめられたら泣いちゃうかもね
I might cry if I'm bullied,
だってそんなのってないぺこちゃん
You wouldn't do that, would you, Pekora?
若いよねだり
You're so young, aren't you?
いっぱい愛をマックスマックス (のえる！もっと！)
Lots of love, max max (Oi! Oi!)
(ペコラ！もっと！) (フレア！もっと！) (マリン！もっと！)
More, hego la (More, play!)
ホロライブファンタジーを愛してる！
I love Hololive Fantasy so much!
君のこと大好き大好き大好き大好き大好き！溢れるこの愛はきっとずっと止まらない
I love you so much, I can't get enough!
あいあいあいあいアイラブユー君があいあいあいあい愛に中！もっともっともっともっとみんなだけ愛させて
I love you, I love you, I love you, 24/7!
ときめくハートごぴょんぴょんぴょん
Heart goes thump-thump-thump,
恋にうたれておんりょうりょう
In love, on a roll!
こんなになったら魔法は解けましん！本気になってる縫い縫い縫い
When it gets this intense, magic is time-released!
行ってもくまであほいあほい！もっともっともっともっと好きなだけ愛してね
Let's just love each other as much as we want!
あいあいあいあいアイラブユー君があいあいあいあい愛に中
Ai-ai-ai-ai, I love you, you are ai-ai-ai-ai, in love 24/7!
あいあいあいあいアイラブユー
Ai-ai-ai-ai, I love you!
私たち愛をもっと
More of our love!
叫べ愛のコール！
Shout out the call of love!
ぴきぴきぴきぴきあほい！(あほい！)ぴかぴかぴかぴかあほい！(あほい！)
Piki-piki, a-hoi! (Piki-piki, a-hoi!)
いろけだったのまりんです！(よーそろー！)
Let's get colored in, it's Marine! (Let's roll!)
ともに脱落、筋肉にま、り、も、しゅ、ぶ、こ、(おどり！)
Dancing together, muscle up and show off!
ない、船長だのたぬきだおめいざ！(さ、た、と、く、そ、)
My leader's a tanuki, third place!
さいきょうめがみえふぇくと！(よっしゃ！)
The strongest goddess effect! (Woo-hoo!)
よしよしして！(よっしゃ！)よくばりめ！よこどりか？(れいぜい！)
Yoshikoshi-shi, let's go! (Yosshaa!)
うさぎか？大成功のため！初心者ホルモンいけちゃう？
First-year hormones, can we do it?
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル！
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol!
直感の阿新感コール！
Pulse racing, heart pounding!
大きまりのファースト好き溢れちゃう！
A definite overflowing of first-sushi love!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル！
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol!
神木もいる？小山いる？もう早い！着替えなの括弧つけてじゃん！
Even Shinki and Kosan are already here!
あいたい！おしたい！(あいたい！おしたい！)現場で全力応援きゅるきゅる！
Aitai! Ositai! (Aitai! Ositai!)
ちあー！ちあー！(ふれ！ふれ！)エール触れ！褒められてリアリス！
Chia! Chia! (Fure! Fure!)
(ふれあ！)あいだり！？(はい、はにー！)
(Fure-fure!) Aifari! (Hai-hany!)
世界で一番愛してる！
Loving you the most in the world!
チャンネル登録なんて無理よ！
Channel subscription? That's impossible!
じょいじょい、えんじょい！団長のノエルなる！
Joy-joy, enjoy! Captain Noel's...?
みるふぅわのきを！泣きしに夜！孤独みたい！ぐらふでのいたい！
Buru-furu, wa-no-ki-o! Naki-shi-ni-yoru!
きゅーどん！(犬続くのタイマディ！)
Kyu-don! (Inu-tsuku no taiming!)
歌しより追いかけよう今日！
Let's chase after you today!
あれ、実質…メンバー？
Are you actually a member?
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル！
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol!
可愛いとか超えてつきこじらせちゃう！
Cute, right? So let's get you hooked!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル！来年からもっと集める！ゲルチ組も！エルセイも！
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol! Let's gather more from next year!
もはやぜいんとして！
No, hurry up and fix it!
現場で全力応援きゅるきゅる！
现场で全力応援きゅるきゅる！
ちあー！ちあー！みんなの王様！
Chia! Chia! (Everyone's queen!)
みんなの歌姫！
Everyone's songstress!
みんなの団長！
Everyone's leader!
みんなの船長！
Everyone's captain!
ラブオンピースな時も推しがへこんだ時でも
Love on piece, even when you're feeling down,
トライあのエラー重ねたい君とみたい景色があるんだ！
That wonderful scenery is calling out!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル！
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol!
直感の阿新感コール！
Pulse racing, heart pounding!
おしまりのファンサで好き溢れちゃい大好き！一生好きだよ！
We're so in love! I love you so much!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル！ラストまでおっかけろ！何年経ってもさ、
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol! Last, let's take it all the way!
存在が最強大勝利！
Existence is the ultimate grand victory!
きゅるきゅるきゅるきゅるアイドル！永遠の愛誓い帰るん！尊い推し、
Kyuru-kyuru-kyuru-kyuru idol! Endless love exchange, I'll miss you!
箱推しはもはや生害おっかけてじゃん！
Boxed-up shyness is old news, so let's get over it!
もうずっともうずっと現場で限界応援きゅるきゅる！
Forever and ever, cheering you on at the venue, kyuru-kyuru!
ジャ！ジャ！
Cha! Cha!
落ち着くために自己紹介しようということで
To calm down, let's do self-introductions.
自己紹介はOK？
Are self-introductions okay?
はい！
Yes!
完璧を完璧を完璧を…ほら、ライブ最初の日でしょ？
Perfect, perfect, perfect... Look, it's the first day of the live, right?
うそだ！手からと、うま、こんぺこって言わしてよ。
No way! Let me say "from the hand, um, con-peko".
言いたい！言いたい！もう一回やってよ！
I want to say it! I want to say it! Do it one more time!
なんて言えばいいの？ペコラは。
What should I say, Pekora?
コンペコ、コンペコ、コンペコつったら、向こうも言いたいんだって！
If you say "con-peko, con-peko, con-peko", they want to say it too!
そういうことね！
Is that so!
じゃあみんなやってくれますか？
Then will everyone do it for us?
完璧を完璧を完璧をー！
Perfect, perfect, perfect!
ほら、ライブ最初の日でしょ？うそだ！手からとっ…
Look, it's the first day of the live, right? No way! From the hand...
はい、じゃあフレアはこうね、じゃなくて、はい、ダー、はい、ダーリンて返してく、さ、い。
Yes, then Flare, not like this, but you return with "Hi, der, hi, darling", please.
はいだ、はいだーりんて返してくーだ、さい！あい！
Return with "Hi, der, hi, darling"! Ple-ase! Ai!
ハイ、ダーリン！ハイ、ハニー！
Hi, darling! Hi, honey!
ありがとう！ホロライブ3期生のしらぬいフレアと…
Thank you! Hololive 3rd Generation's Shiranui Flare and...
はい、じゃあ、なんちょうは、ええ、牛丼はって言うんで、何も無いのはって言ってください！なにもないだから！じゃあいくよ！牛丼はー？
Yes, then, Nanchou is, uh, gyudon is, so please say "There's nothing"! Because there's nothing! Okay, here we go! Gyudon isー?
牛丼のないやーつ！
The gyudon-less kind!
ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルと…
Hololive 3rd Generation's Shirogane Noel and...
君たち、今もしかして、フレアのことハニーって言った？
You guys, did you just call Flare "honey"?
お前たち、お前たち！よろよろ！何のことか忘れてしまってるぞ、君たち！
You guys, you guys! Yoroyoro! You've forgotten what it's about, you guys!
なんちゃって。え、じゃあどうしようかな。あ、じゃあ、普通にアホイで行きますんで、アホイって言ってくださいね！
Just kidding. Uh, then what should I do? Ah, then, since we'll just go with Ahoy normally, please say Ahoy!
アホイ！アホイ！
Ahoy! Ahoy!
誰がアホやねん！
Who's the fool!
なんちゃって！え、ホロライブ3期生、宝鐘海賊団船長の宝鐘マリンです！
Just kidding! Uh, I'm Houshou Marine, captain of the Houshou Pirates, Hololive 3rd Generation!
みんなこそ。
You guys too.
みんななんかアイドル工場みたいなさ、ブースでしたやつはやる？やる？
Everyone, like an idol factory booth, are you gonna do it? Are you?
やろうよ！やろうよ！これはやるしかないわ！じゃあまた、順番で。
Let's do it! Let's do it! We have to do this! Then again, in order.
あ、順番で行きましょう、順番で。オッケー。
Ah, let's go in order, in order. Okay.
みんな覚えてるよね？ペコラの工場！絶対覚えてねえぞ！覚えているよね、ちゃんと、覚えてる人、挙手して！
Everyone remembers, right? Pekora's factory! You definitely don't remember! You remember, right? Everyone who remembers, raise your hand!
あ、でも、めっちゃ、めっちゃ上がってるね！全然上がってないやん！全然覚えてねえって！
Ah, but a lot, a lot are raised! Not raised at all! You guys remember nothing at all!
じゃあ、今から覚えてくださいね！じゃあ、ペコラから行きますよ！ラビット、キャロット、キラッと登場、最強アイドルペコラがキタペコ！まだまだ続くよ！ペコラスター！
Well then, learn it from now on! Okay, starting from Pekora! Rabbit, carrot, sparkling appearance, the strongest idol Pekora has arrived peko! It's still going! Pekora Star!
ちょっと、フレア、めっちゃ難しいんだけどさ、いけるかな、これ。いけるいける！みんなもあの、掛け声、よろしくね！これ、あの、みんなにもコールアンドレスポンスしてほしくて、あの、準備は？って言ったら、
Wait, Flare, it's super difficult, can we do it? We can, we can! Everyone, please give us your call-and-response! We want you to do a call-and-response, so when I say "Ready?",
バンタン！バンタン！ホールわ？って聞くので、簡単！って言ってくださいね！で、手拍子、パンパン！パンパンパン！ステップ、簡単！
Bantan! Bantan! When I ask "Hollu is?", please say "Kantan!" And clapping, pan-pan! Pan-pan-pan! Step, kantan!
私は、フッ…
I am, fu...
めっちゃ難しいな！めちゃくちゃ、これ練習ね！練習、お、覚えてください。はい。
Super difficult! Super messy, this is practice! Practice, oh, please remember. Yes.
こんぬい！準備はー？
Konnui! Ready?
ばんたん！
Bantan!
ホールわー？かんたん！
Hollu is? Kantan!
手拍子、ぱんぱん、すてっぷ、かんたん！
Clapping, pan-pan, step, kantan!
私は、ふんだん！
I am, fundan!
ホロライブ3期生、きらねんフレアです！
Hololive 3rd Generation, Shiranui Flare!
すごい！すごーい！
Amazing! So ama-zing!
ありがとう！難しいのに、すごいですよ！じゃあ次はノエルから！
Thank you! It's difficult, but you're amazing! Next is Noel!
ノエル行きます！団長とコールアンドレスポンスないから、ちょっとラップします！
Noel's going! Since the captain and I don't have a call-and-response, I'll rap a bit!
ちょっとここからね。ここから行こうかな。歩く。
Let's start from here. Let's go from here. Walking.
行きます！毎日いつもしっかりのごはんの食べ物は牛丼！おのしで飲み物はみんなのきゅうこん！ダメダメ急コン！ホロライブ3期生の白銀ノエルでーす！
Here we go! Every day always proper food is gyudon! With that, drinks are everyone's proposal! No-no urgent proposal! I'm Shirogane Noel of Hololive 3rd Generation!
え、マリン、まあ、コールスなんで先に予習しましょうか。
Um, well, since there are callouts, let's pre-study first!
え、マリンが、マリンが、って言ったら、次は、
When Marine says "Marine, Marine", next—
「船長！」で、マリンが……
You say "Captain!" And when Marine...
「船長！」で、
"Captain!"
「船長！」で、君らは？
"Captain!" And you guys are?
「いちみ！」
"Ichimi!"
我ら無敵の！「海賊団！」
We are the invincible! "Pirate crew!"
で、最後に「宝箱開けちゃって宝箱の、マリンです」って言うから、そしたら、問答無用で「かわいい！」って言う。わかりましたね？
And at the end, I'll say "I opened the treasure chest, I'm Marine," so then without a word, you say "So cute!" Got it?
ま、余裕だよね。じゃあ、もう一回練習しといて、じゃあ行くわよ！マリンは？
Well, piece of cake, right? Let's practice once more, so here we go! Marine is?
「船長！」
"Captain!"
君らは？
And you guys?
「いちみ！」
"Ichimi!"
我ら無敵の！「海賊団！」宝箱開けちゃって宝箱の、マリンです！「かわいい！」
We are the invincible! "Pirate crew!" Captain Marine who opened the treasure chest! "So cute!"
「かわいい！」
"So cute!"
いや、気持ちいいよね、これね。そんなかわいい？
Man, that feels great, doesn't it? Is it really that cute?
よかったな、かわいいって言われてよかったな。そんなことないけど。
Good for you, glad you were told you're cute. Not really, though.
でもちっとコール＆レスポンスね、ちょっと、1発目からもうすごい難しいのやらしちゃってどうもすみませんね。ねえ、たくさんちょっとありがとう、ありがとう！
But call and response, sorry for making it so difficult right from the first one! Thank you so much, thank you!
え、声が聞こえますよ、叩きまして。
Oh, I can hear your voices, you're clapping.
さっきのさ、うちらのエンジン聞こえました？聞こえた？
Did you hear our engine from earlier? Did you hear it?
あ、聞こえた？聞こえた？よかった。
Ah, you heard it? You heard it? Yay!
ちょっと、なんか聞こえるかなって不安だったの。
I was a bit worried if you could hear it.
こっちにはね、君らの声よく聞こえるんだけど、さすがにマイク返さないと小さかったかなと思って。でもお腹から出した、お腹から、ねえ。
Over here, we can hear your voices really well, but I thought maybe without returning mics, it'd be too quiet. But we pushed from our guts, right?
あ、聞こえた？聞こえるよ、こっちにも声聞こえてますよ。
Ah, you heard it? We can hear you, we can hear your voices over here too.
衣装のことも言わなきゃ。そうだよ。二人からめちゃんこ可愛かったけど、突然の新衣装、可愛いでしょう？ちょっとずつ違うところがありますんで。
We gotta talk about our outfits too. That's right. Both of them were super cute, but our sudden new outfits are cute, right? There are little differences here and there.
ペコーラは耳輪がついているペコで。
Pekora has a bunny ring attached, peko.
輪っかがついているペコで、なんと、初案者はノエちゃん。
A ring is attached, and surprisingly, the original proposer is Noel-chan.
そう、ノエる、すごいでしょう、可愛い。
That's right, Noel, amazing, right? Cute.
マリンはね、ヘッドドレスがね、ほら、こんな感じで、バツバツバツバツバツ…待ってね、ランチャーなんかポンポン付いてます。
Marine's head-dress, look, like this, cross cross cross... wait, it has launcher-like pom-poms attached.
ノエちゃんは、この頭のリボンかな？可愛いね。
Noel-chan, is this ribbon on her head? So cute.
フレアは、この頭のリボンかな？可愛いね、二人とも違いますね。だからも蹴る、蹴る、蹴るです。
Flare, is this ribbon on her head? So cute, they're both different. So kick, kick, kick!
ギャルです。ギャルです。
It's gal style. Gal style.
皆さん、あの、うちらね、結構めちゃめちゃしゃべりすぎてるみたいで。
Everyone, um, it seems like we've been talking way too much.
このまま音楽失わないのかいみたいな感じ。
Like, are we not gonna lose the music?
そうだね。
That's right.
ちなみにあの配信でね見てる方、あのYouTubeで見てる方、あの概要欄にね配信チケットのリンクありますので。
By the way, for those watching on the stream, those watching on YouTube, there's a streaming ticket link in the description box, so please—
次の曲でちょっとチラ見せは終わりペコなので今のうちに。
The sneak peek ends with the next song, so while you can.
まだまだ見てほしいパートがいっぱいあるんです！お願いします！朝たか蹴るんだ大作戦、デイワンでいっぱいつぶやいてね。
There are still so many parts we want you to see! Please! The "Asataka Kerunnda" grand operation, tweet a lot on Day 1!
生バンドがね、すごいかっこいいじゃん？そう、だからちょっと聞きたくて。
The live band is super cool, right? Yeah, so we wanted to hear it.
じゃあ、ペコラちゃんからいってもらっていいですか？
So, Pekora-chan, could you go first?
了解！え、エアバンドキーボード担当、嘘だペコラ！
Understood! Um, air band keyboard, Usada Pekora!
すげえ！
Amazing!
よし、いくよ。ギター、宝鐘マリン！
Alright, here we go. Guitar, Houshou Marine!
おお！かっこいい！
Oh! Cool!
はい、え、ドラム、白銀ノエル！
Yes, um, drums, Shirogane Noel!
やばい、かっこよ！
Wow, so cool!
じゃあ、フレア、ベースやります！
Next, Flare, playing bass!
かっこいいわ！最高！
So cool! Awesome!
私らが演奏してます！演奏してるよん！
We are playing! We're performing!
あ、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょうか！場所、場所、場所、場所、ここ。
Ah, well, shall we move on to the next song soon? Spot, spot, spot, spot, here.
はい、じゃあそろそろ次の曲行きましょう！せーの！リアルティファンタジー！
Alright, let's go to the next song soon! Ready, go! Reality Fantasy!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！さあ！
Adventure! Set sail! Now! Challenge! Start! Now! Adventure! Set sail! Now! Challenge! Start! Now!
お宝探しに大海原 いざ出航だ！
Setting sail into the open sea in search of treasure!
さあ、挑戦！開始！
Now, let the challenge begin!
身も心からも ぴょんぴょん わくわく
Body and soul, bounding and excited,
ちょっぴり ドキドキ
with a little bit of nervousness.
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！
Adventure! Set out! Now! Challenge! Start!
吸いへい線の向こう側
Beyond the horizon,
新天地 待っててね
wait for us, new world!
運命なんかなり飛び越して その先へ！
Jump right over fate and head beyond!
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー ふたつの狭間へ
Now, into the gap between reality and fantasy,
夢歌え 超えちゃおう 一緒に
sing of dreams, let's surpass them together!
さあ まだ見ない世界へと 君を連れてくよ
Now, I'll take you to a world you've never seen,
みんなが繋がる物語に
into a story where everyone connects!
さあ 始まるよ 冒険 出発！ さあ 挑戦 開始！
Now it begins! Adventure, set out! Now, the challenge starts!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！
Adventure! Set out! Now! Challenge! Start!
みんないこころざし同じ 一期一会の騎士団集合
Knights sharing aspirations, a once-in-a-lifetime assembly!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！
Adventure! Set out! Now! Challenge! Start!
胸に宿る太陽 風を切って さらに輝け！
The sun in your chest, cut through the wind and shine brighter!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！
Adventure! Set out! Now! Challenge! Start!
迷いそうと夢 晴天に行き着けたら 突撃だー！
If our wandering dreams reach clear skies, charge ahead!
寄って立ちこの旅見守って
Stop by and watch over this journey.
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー ふたつの狭間へ 放り上げて 歌えユートピアへ
Reality, fantasy, toss it up into the gap and sing to utopia!
さあ それぞれの世界から 鍵音を超えたら
Now, transcending the key sounds from each world,
みんなが繋がる物語に
into a story where everyone connects
さあ 始まるよ 明るく陽気に 新たみ乗り越え ホーロー ライブ！
Now it begins! Cheerfully and brightly, Hololive Live!
愛嬌開放 うさ耳にすまして ホーロー ライブ！
Charm unleashed, listen with rabbit ears, Hololive Live!
気高き誇り 胸に刻んだら ホーロー ライブ！
Noble pride carved in your chest, Hololive Live!
神話に伝わる 神秘の囁き ホーロー ライブ！
Mystical whispers from myths, Hololive Live!
冒険！出発！さあ！挑戦！開始！
Adventure! Set out! Now! Challenge! Start!
さあ リアリティ ファンタジー ふたつの狭間へ
Now, into the gap between reality and fantasy,
夢歌え 超えちゃおう 一緒に
sing of dreams, let's surpass them together!
さあ まだ見ない世界へと 君を連れてくよ
Now, I'll take you to a world you've never seen,
準備はほらできたよ ルートも先回りだよ みんなが繋がる物語に
Preparations are ready, route scouted, into a story connecting all!
さあ 始まるよ
Now it begins!
時は2026年 2回目の3期生ライブ！
The year is 2026, our 2nd 3rd-generation live!
このチャンスを逃してなるものか！
There's no way we're letting this chance slip away!
今こそ全人類うさイイっけ計画を遂行する！
Now is the time to execute the all-humanity rabbit plan!